[{"question": " oh my god! i can\u0092t believe my little brother is married!", "answer": " oh i know!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " you guys, why didn\u0092t you tell me you were eloping?", "answer": " \u0091cause it just sorta happened, y\u0092know we were at the courthouse, we were having lunch\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " wait, wait, why were you at the courthouse?", "answer": " we were having lunch. yeah and then all of the sudden we were like, \"hey! y'know, we\u0092re here, having lunch let\u0092s get married!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " wow, a year and a half ago i didn\u0092t even know i had a brother, and now i have a sister too.  okay. okay. stop it, don\u0092t. so, i gotta get you a gift now. is there anything you need?", "answer": " uhh, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " we\u0092ve been trying to get pregnant, uh pretty much ever since we got engaged, we thought we\u0092d get a jump on things, y\u0092know no one\u0092s getting any younger.", "answer": " see the thing is umm, we\u0092re not able to y\u0092know, uh, conceive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " and we\u0092ve tried everything, we\u0092ve seen a bunch of doctors.", "answer": " yeah, and they-and they say that our-that our only chance to have a baby is that if they take my sperm, her egg and put it together in a dish and then put it into another girl. so we were wondering if you could be the girl that we could put it into.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  hey! you guys! check it out, check it out!  guess which job i got.", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, but donald trump wants his blue blazer black.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " blue blazer back. he-he wants it back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " but you-you said black. why would he want his blue blazer black?", "answer": " well, you-you know what i meant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " no, you messed it up. you\u0092re stupid.", "answer": " so what job did you get joe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " oh, ah, tour guide at the museum. yeah, ross got it for me.", "answer": " well, how can you be a tour guide, don\u0092t you have to be a dinosaur expert or something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " no, not really. they give you all the information, it\u0092s uh, it\u0092s like memorizing a script.  \"and on your left, you have tyrannosaurus rex, a carnivore from the jurassic period. chandler, monica, and rachel: great!! that\u0092s great!", "answer": " uh actually joey, it\u0092s the cretasous period.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " yeah but, i can pronounce jurassic.", "answer": "  hey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " guess what. frank jr., and alice got married!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " oh my god!!", "answer": " and! and, they\u0092re gonna have a baby!  and! and, they want me to grow it for them in my uterus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " my god!", "answer": " are you serious?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " yeah", "answer": " you\u0092re really thinking about having sex with your brother?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " ewww! and \"oh no!\" it\u0092s\u0097they just want me to be the surrogate. it\u0092s her-it\u0092s her egg and her sperm, and i\u0092m-i\u0092m just the oven, it\u0092s totally their bun.", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " what did you tell them?", "answer": " well, they said that i had to think about it first, but what is there to think about? i\u0092m gonna be giving them the greatest gift you can possibly give.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " you\u0092re gonna be carrying their baby and give them a sony play station?", "answer": " honey, this really is an incredible thing to do for them, but there are things to think about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " yeah, like you\u0092re gonna be pregnant. i mean pregnant.", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " pheebs, you\u0092re talking about putting your body through an awful lot, i mean morning sickness, uhh, labour, and it\u0092s all for somebody else!", "answer": " yeah, what\u0092s your point?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " well, the stuff i just mentioned.", "answer": " wow! i don\u0092t know if i could ever do that. i always figured the first time i had a baby was with somebody i love and that baby would be a\u009akeeper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " y'know you guys were a lot more supportive when i wanted to make denim furniture.", "answer": " no, pheebs, listen, if you decide to do this, we\u0092ll be supportive like crazy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " we just want you to think it through.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah, honey, maybe you can talk to somebody who\u0092s had a baby. like your mom?", "answer": " my mom never gave birth. oh! but my birth mom did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " umm,  i love this touchy. can i take it to work with me?", "answer": " oh, yeah, sure, it\u0092s not mine anyway. it can with the pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " i am so jealous.", "answer": " you guys are really right\u009athere aren\u0092t you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " yes. right where?", "answer": " in the beginning where y\u0092know it\u0092s all sex and talking and sex and talking and\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " yeah, you-you gotta love the talking.", "answer": " and the sex?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " all right, we haven\u0092t had sex yet. okay, what\u0092s the big deal? y\u0092know? this is special, and i want our love to grow until we move on to the next level.", "answer": " oh, chandler that is so nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " that is really nice\u009alying! no way is that the reason!", "answer": " why? just because you\u0092re not mature enough to understand something like that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " then what is it?", "answer": " well, kathy\u0092s last boyfriend was joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " and you\u0092re afraid you won\u0092t be able to\u009afill his shoes.", "answer": " no, i\u0092m afraid i won\u0092t be able to make love as well as him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " yeah, i was going for the metaphor.", "answer": " yes, and i was saying the actual words.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " so big deal, so joey\u0092s had a lot of girlfriends, it doesn\u0092t mean he\u0092s great in bed.", "answer": " we share a wall! so either he\u0092s great in bed, or she just likes to agree with him a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " sweetie, with you it\u0092s gonna be different. the sex is gonna be great, \u0091cause you-you guys are in love.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " just go for it chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yeah, you should.", "answer": " yeah, you should, really.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " go on.", "answer": " all right, all right, i\u0092ll go sleep with my girlfriend. but i\u0092m just doing it for you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " okay, now the mastodon is from the semi-late jurassic period.", "answer": " isn\u0092t the mastodon from the pliocene epic?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " it\u0092s open! come in!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i\u0092m late.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh, that\u0092s okay, it gave me time to finish glazing my nipples.", "answer": " wow! you really go all out when you\u0092re expecting company.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " no, i was working on my pottery.", "answer": " oh! ooh! oh, i didn\u0092t know that you did\u009apot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " well, yeah, mostly nudes. it combines my two passions, pottery and erotica.", "answer": " ooh, erotiery!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " hey! okay! well thanks for coming out to see me. i just-i just thought it would be a very good idea to talk about this baby stuff in person. y\u0092know\u009a", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i really don\u0092t think it\u0092s a very good idea, phoebe.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh no! no-no! i understand the pain! don\u0092t-don\u0092t hurt the puppy.", "answer": " no-no-no, the-the puppy\u0092s yours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh, i get a puppy!!", "answer": " well, yeah! i mean yeah, but only for three days.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " i realise i don\u0092t have any right to start get all parenty on you and everything now, but umm,  uhh\u009a phoebe, would you please look at me and not the puppy, it\u0092s very important.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " i mean, i know what i\u0092m talking about. i gave up two babies, and i only wish i had someone there that had given up babies, that could tell me how terrible it is to give up babies. i just think that, it would be something you will regret every single day for the rest of your life. so, how ever hard it is to give up this puppy, it would be like a million times harder to give up a child.  i really shouldn\u0092t have given you the puppy first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " uhh, do you mind sitting there. i\u0092m-i\u0092m saving this for my friend ross.", "answer": " you mean dr. geller?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " doctor? wow! i didn\u0092t know he had a nickname.", "answer": " oh, he won\u0092t sit here. only the people in the white coats sit over there,  and only the people in the blue blazers sit here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " well, how-how come?", "answer": " that\u0092s just the way it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " that\u0092s crazy.", "answer": " maybe it\u0092s crazy in a perfect world, a world without lab coats and blazers, but you not in a perfect world, you in a museum now. see that scientist in the classes, he and i used to play together all the time in grade school, but now\u009a peter! hey, peter! it\u0092s me rhonda! from ps-129! i shared my puddin\u0092 which you man! i gave you my snack pack!  see, he pretend he don\u0092t even here me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i-i think everybody\u0092s pretending they don\u0092t hear you. anyway, look, i don\u0092t know about you and your jackets and your separate tables, but ross is one of my best friends, and if i save him a seat, i\u0092m telling you, he will sit in it!  ross! ross! over here, man! i-i saved you seat.", "answer": " that\u0092s okay, i\u0092m cool over here. i\u0092ll catch up with you later, joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  hey, uh, i\u0092m really, really sorry about what happened in the cafeteria today.", "answer": " it\u0092s no big deal. hey, y\u0092know, you do what you gotta do. right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " but hey, it\u0092s not just me, i mean the scientists and the tour guides never sit together.", "answer": " whatever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " it\u0092s like that everywhere, joey! okay, mon, back me up here. where you work the uh, waiters eat with the waiters, right? and the chefs eat with the other chefs, right?", "answer": " i eat by myself in the alley because everybody hates me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " why is phoebe singing to carl mulden?", "answer": " ooh, y\u0092know what, i think it\u0092s time for puppy to go out again. come on, let\u0092s go to the balcony.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " umm, the street. come on, let\u0092s go to the street. ooh, listen, don\u0092t go onto the balcony until after i get back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  so, did you do it?", "answer": " yes, yes, we had the sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " uh-oh, it was bad?", "answer": " it was fine, y\u0092know? but she didn\u0092t agree with me as strongly as she agreed with joey. she was more like, \"i see you point, i\u0092m all right with it.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " well, it was the first time. y\u0092know, there\u0092s not always a lot of agreement the first time.", "answer": " yeah, not girls anyway, guys agree  like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " look, you have to help me! okay? i mean, i know what to do with a woman, y\u0092know, i know where everything goes, it\u0092s always nice. but i need to know what makes it go from nice to, \"my god! somebody\u0092s killing her in there!\"", "answer": " all right, i\u0092m gonna show you something a lot of guys don\u0092t know. rach, give me that pad, please?  all right. now\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " look, you don\u0092t have to draw an actual wo\u0097whoa! she\u0092s hot!", "answer": " now everybody knows the basic erogenous zones.  you got one, two three, four , five, six, and seven!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  there are seven?!", "answer": " let me see that.  oh, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  that\u0092s one?", "answer": " it\u0092s kind of an important one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh, y\u0092know-y\u0092know what, i was looking at it upside down.", "answer": " well, y\u0092know, sometimes that helps.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  now, most guys will hit uh, 1-2-3 and then go to 7 and set up camp.", "answer": " that-that\u0092s bad?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " well if you go to disneyland, you don\u0092t spend the whole day on the materhorn.", "answer": " well you might if it were anything like 7!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " all right uh, the important thing is to take your time, you want to hit \u0091em all, and you mix \u0091em up. you gotta keep them on their toes.", "answer": " oo, toes!! well, for some people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " thank you, dr. phillips, but i\u0092m having my lunch at this table, here in the middle. i\u0092m having lunch right here, with my good friend joey, if he\u0092ll sit with me.", "answer": "  i will sit with you dr. geller.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " y'know, we work in a museum of natural history, and yet there is something unnatural about the way we eat lunch. now, i look around this cafeteria, and y\u0092know what i see, i see-i see division. division, between people in white coats and people in blue blazers, and i ask myself, \"my god why?!\" now, i say we shed these-these coats that separate us, and we get to know the people underneath.  i\u0092m ross! i\u0092m divorced, and i have a kid!", "answer": "  i\u0092m joey! i\u0092m an actor! i don\u0092t know squat about dinosaurs! another tour guide:  i\u0092m ted, and i just moved here a month ago, and new york really scares me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " all right, there you go!", "answer": " yeah, you hang in there teddy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " i\u0092m andrew, and i didn\u0092t pay for this pear.", "answer": " okay, good-good for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " wow, rhonda.", "answer": " i\u0092m scott.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " yeah, okay, scott!", "answer": " and i need to flip the light switch on and off 17 times before i leave a room or my family will die.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " my mom\u0092s gonna be here any minute. i can\u0092t do this, i can\u0092t give him up. yes\u0097no, i can. i don\u0092t want to. but i can. no.", "answer": " oo, i can\u0092t watch this, it\u0092s like sophie\u0092s choice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " y\u0092know, i never saw that.", "answer": " ooh, it was only okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " ooh, i can\u0092t do this. my mom was right. if i can\u0092t-if i can\u0092t give him up, then there\u0092s no way i can give up a baby. ohh, god, frank and alice are gonna be so crushed. what-what else, what else can i give \u0091em\u0097a kidney!", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " uhh, we were just in the neighbourhood, so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yeah, so we just thought we\u0092d stop by and let you know there\u0092s still no pressure.", "answer": " none. but if there was something you wanted to tell us, we\u0092re just gonna be right over there  having coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": "  oh, who\u0092s this little guy?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " oh! ooh! umm!", "answer": " oh, he\u0092s so cute, he reminds me of my old dog, tumour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " you are so precious, i could just take you home.", "answer": " hey, why don\u0092t you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " are you serious?", "answer": " uh-huh, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh, thanks.", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " no, i\u0092m really okay with this. y\u0092know why? \u0091cause look at them, and i made that, so\u009a i know it\u0092s gonna be like a million times harder to give up a baby but, oh my god, it\u0092s gonna feel like a million times better, right? i wanna do this.  i wanna carry your baby.", "answer": "  oh! oh! oh! thank you so much! you don\u0092t know what this means to us! oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh my god, i think i\u0092m gonna cry!", "answer": " it\u0092s gonna be so great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  hi! what\u0092s going on?", "answer": " oh, i-i gave them the puppy and it made them so happy that i decided i\u0092m gonna carry their baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " but phoebe\u009a", "answer": " no-no-no, i know, but you and i are different people though, and this is a totally different situation, and i know that i am not gonna regret this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " oh, i-i-i understand all that, but it\u0092s just\u0097that was my puppy.", "answer": " oh! closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " would you ever be a surrogate for anyone?", "answer": " it depends on who asked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " what if i asked?", "answer": " oh, mon, sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yes.  you\u0092re not asking are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " yes! totally!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}]